A Guide to the Christian de Duve papers, Rockefeller University Faculty, Accession 2009:084 FA934
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Imanaka, Small and Lazarow, Translocation of Acyl-Coa Oxidase into Peroxisomes Requires ATP Hydrolysis but Not a Membrane Potential, 1987 (Box 41)
- Perkins and Holt, Erythrocyte Receptor Recognition Varies in Plasmodium falciparum Isolates, 1988 (Box 41)
- de Duve, Christian, Prebiotic Syntheses and the Mechanism of Early Chemical Evolution, 1988 (Box 41)
- de Duve, Christian, RNAs- The Second Genetic Code, 1988 (Box 41)
- de Duve, Christian, Did God Make RNA?, 1988 (Box 41)
- Sam-Yellowe, et al., Secretion of Plasmodium falciparum Rhoptry Protein into the Plasma Membrane of Host Erythrocytes, 1988 (Box 41)
- Small, et al., Peroxisomal Integral Membrane Proteins in Livers of Patients with Zellweger Syndrome, Infantile Refsum's Disease and X-linked Adrenoleukodystrophy, 1988 (Box 41)
- Perkins, Stage-Dependent Processing and Localization of a Plasmodium falciparum Protein of 130,000 Molecular Weight, 1988 (Box 41)
- Perkins and Rocco, Sialic Acid-Dependent Binding of Plasmodium falciparum Merozoite Surface Antigen, Pf200, to Human Erythrocytes, 1988 (Box 41)
- Müller, Lossick, and Gorrell, In vitro Susceptibility of Trichomonas vaginalis to Metronidazole and Treatment Outcome in Vaginal Trichomoniasis, 1988 (Box 41)
- Müller, Energy Metabolism of Protozoa Without Mitochondria, 1988 (Box 41)
- Lazarow, Peroxisomes, 1988 (Box 41)
- Small, Imanaka, Lazarow, How Are Peroxisomal Proteins Directed to and Imported Peroxisomes?, 1988 (Box 41)
- Lazarow, Small and Imanaka, Biogenesis of Enzymes of Peroxisomal B-Oxidation, 1988 (Box 41)
- Small, Szabo and Lazarow, Acyl-Coa Oxidase Contains Two Targeting Sequences Each of Which Can Mediate Protein Import into Peroxisomes, 1988 (Box 41)
- Small, Imanaka and Lazarow, Immunoblotting of Hydrophobic Integral Membrane Proteins, 1988 (Box 41)
- Santos, et al, Peroxisomal Membrane Ghosts in Zellweger Syndrome- Aberrant Organelle Assembly, 1988 (Box 41)
- Santos, et al., Peroxisomal Integral Membrane Protein in Control and Zellweger Fibroblasts, 1988 (Box 41)
- Lazarow, et al, Zellweger Syndrome Amniocytes- Morphological Appearance and a Simple Sedimentation Method for Pre-natal Diagnosis, 1988 (Box 41)
- de Duve, Christian, The Biological Revolution in Medical Research, 1988 (Box 41)
- Glass Slides, B. Poole (Box 41)
- Glass Slides, Unlabeled (Box 41)
- Reprint Index Cards (Box 41)
- Reprints, 1973 (Box 42)
- Reprints, 1975 (Box 42)
- Reprints, 1975-1976 (Box 42)
- Reprints, 1975 (Box 43)
- Reprints, 1976-1977 (Box 43)
- Miscellaneous Glass and Plastic Slides (Box 44)
- Audio Cassette Tapes (Box 44)
- Wood Block Plates (Box 44)
- Missing Reprints, 1-3 (Box 45)
- Reprints, 4-12, 1964-1966 (Box 45)
- Missing Reprints, 13-14 (Box 45)
- Reprints, 15-31, 1966-1968 (Box 45)
- Reprints, 32-41, 1968-1969 (Box 45)
- Reprints, 42-50, 1969 (Box 46)
- Reprints, 51-67, 1969-1971 (Box 46)
- Reprints, 68-77, 1971 (Box 46)
- Reprints, 78-87, 1972-1973 (Box 47)
- Reprints, 88-95, 1973 (Box 47)
- Missing Reprints, 96-112 (Box 47)
- Reprints, 113-123, 1974 (Box 47)
- Missing Reprint, 124 (Box 48)
- Reprints, 125-134, 1975 (Box 48)
- Reprints, 214-236, 1978-1979 (Box 48)
- Reprints, 237-253, 1978-1979 (Box 48)
- Reprints, 254-269, 1979 (Box 48)
- Reprints, 270-291, 1979-1980 (Box 48)
- Reprints, 292-309, 1980-1981 (Box 49)
- Reprints, 310-322, 1981 (Box 49)
- Reprints, 323-335, 1981 (Box 49)
- Reprints, 336-346, 1982 (Box 49)
- Reprints, 347-361, 1982 (Box 49)
- Missing Reprints, 362-364 (Box 49)
- Reprints, 364-378, 1983 (Box 49)
- Reprints, 379-395, 1984 (Box 50)
- Reprints, 396-409, 1985 (Box 50)
- Reprints, 410-421, 1986 (Box 50)
- Reprints, A-H, 1965 (Box 50)
- Reprints, I-S, 1965 (Box 50)
- Reprints, T-Z and A-C, 1965-1966 (Box 50)
- Reprints, D-L, 1966 (Box 51)
- Reprints, M-Se, 1966 (Box 51)
- Reprints, Sf-Z, 1966 (Box 51)
- Reprints, A-G, 1967 (Box 51)
- Reprints, H-Q, 1967 (Box 51)
- Reprints, R-Z, 1967 (Box 52)
- Reprints, A-Da, 1968 (Box 52)
- Reprints, Db-L, 1968 (Box 52)
- Reprints, M-Z, 1968 (Box 52)
- Reprints, A-Ch, 1969 (Box 52)
- Reprints, Ci-E, 1969 (Box 52)
- Reprints, F-K, 1969 (Box 53)
- Reprints, L-P, 1969 (Box 53)
- Reprints, Q-Z, 1969 (Box 53)
- Reprints, A-D, 1970 (Box 53)
- Reprints, E-M, 1970 (Box 53)
- Reprints, N-Sm, 1970 (Box 53)
- Reprints, So-Z, 1970 (Box 54)
- Reprints, A-D, 1971 (Box 54)
- Reprints, E-L, 1971 (Box 54)
- Reprints, M-R, 1971 (Box 54)
- Reprints, S-Z, 1971 (Box 54)
- Reprints, A-F, 1972 (Box 55)
- Reprints, G-L, 1972 (Box 55)
- Reprints, M-Q, 1972 (Box 55)
- Reprints, R-Z, 1972 (Box 55)
- Reprints, A-K, 1973 (Box 55)
- Reprints, L-R, 1973 (Box 56)
- Reprints, S-Z, 1973 (Box 56)
- Reprints, A-L, 1974 (Box 56)
- Reprints, M-Z, 1974 (Box 56)
- Reprints, A-L, 1975 (Box 56)
- Reprints, M-Z, 1975 (Box 57)
- Reprints, 1976 (Box 57)
- Reprints, 1977 (Box 57)
- Reprints, A-F (Box 57)
- Reprints, G-N (Box 57)
- Reprints, P-Z (Box 58)
- Reprint, Christian de Duve, "The Peroxisome in Retrospect", 1996 (Box 58)
- Reprint, Meldolesi, et al., "Cytoplasmic Membranes and the Secretory Process,", 1978 (Box 58)
- Reprint, DePierre and Ernster, "Enzyme Topology of Intra-Cellular Membranes", 1977 (Box 58)
- Reprint, DePierre and Ernster, "The Metabolism of Polycyclic Hydrocarbons and its Relationship to Caner", 1978 (Box 58)
- Article, Christian de Duve, "The Onset of Selection", 2005 (Box 58)
- Progress Reports to the Andrew W. Mellon Foundation, 2005 (Box 58)
- Reprint, Christian de Duve, "Constraints on the Origin and Evolution of Life", 1998 (Box 58)
- Rockefeller University (RU) Photographic Directories, 1970-1973 (Box 58)
- Reprint, Christian de Duve and Miller, "Two-Dimensional Life?", 1991 (Box 58)
- Reprint, Christian de Duve, "Prelude to a Cell: Life Began with a Primitive Metabolism in the Primeval Soup", 1990 (Box 58)
- Reprint, Christian de Duve, "Life and its Origin", 1990 (Box 58)
- Reprint, Christian de Duve, "The Birth of Complex Cells", 1996 (Box 58)
- Essay, Christian de Duve, "The Constraints of Chance," Scientific American, 1996 (Box 58)
- Reprint, Christian de Duve, "The Beginnings of Life on Earth", 1995 (Box 58)
- Miscellaneous Reprints, 1992-1994 (Box 58)
- Reprint, Christian de Duve, "Peroxisomes and Related Particles in Historical Perspective", 1982 (Box 58)
- Reprint, Christian de Duve, "Fritz Lipmann: In Memoriam", 1986 (Box 58)
- Reprint, Christian de Duve, "The Future of Experimental Biology in Medical Research", 1986 (Box 58)
- Reprint, Ohkuma, Chudzik, Poole, "The Effect of Basic Substances and Acidic Ionophores on the Digestion of Exogenous and Endogenous Proteins in Mouse Peritoneal Macrophanges", 1986 (Box 58)
- Reprint, Christian Duve and Beaufay, "A Short History of Tissue Fractionation", 1981 (Box 58)
- Reprint, Christian de Duve, "Microbodies in the Living Cell", 1983 (Box 58)
- Reprint, Christian de Duve, "Selection by Differential Molecular Survival: A Possible Mechanism of Early Chemical Evolution", 1987 (Box 58)
- Reprint, Christian de Duve, "The Second Genetic Code", 1987 (Box 58)
- Reprint, Christian de Duve, "Exploring Cells with a Centrifuge", 1974 (Box 58)
- Rockefeller University (RU) Publications, 1961-1979 (Box 58)
- Rockefeller University (RU) Photographic Directories, 1967-1974 (Box 58)
- Publication, Fonds National de la Recherche Scintifique, 1927-1961 (Box 58)
- Publication, Commission Nationale por l'Etude des Problemes que Posent a la Belgiue, et aux Territoires D'Outre-Mer les Progres des Sciences et leurs Reprocussions Economiques et Sociales, 1957 (Box 58)
- Publication, Francqui Fonds, 1957 (Box 58)
- Reprint, Christian de Duve, "The Second Genetic Code", 1988 (Box 58)
- Index Cards, Articles by Author's Names, 1950-1970 (Box 59)
- Rockefeller University (RU) Directory Cards (Box 59)
- Rockefeller University (RU) Directory Cards (Box 59)
- Index Cards, Lectures and Publications, By Name of Author or Organization, 1960-1970 (Box 59)
- Glass Slides, B. Poole (Box 59)
- The Rockefeller University Research Profiles, Christian de Duve and Donald Pfaff, 1984, 1989 (Box 60)
- National Institutes of Health (NIH), Information Exchange Group 1, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1966-1967 (Box 60)
- Charts, Graphs, and Related Notes (Box 60)
- Citations from E. Metchnikoff (Box 60)
- Documentation, Dingle and Fell, 1968 (Box 60)
- The Rockefeller University Faculty and Student Handbook, 1971-1982 (Box 60)
- Rockefeller University (RU), Directory of Graduates:, 1972-1982 (Box 60)
- Miscellaneous Rockefeller University (RU) Publications, 1972-1989 (Box 60)
- Miscellaneous Rockefeller University (RU) Publications, 1969-1988 (Box 60)
- Reprint, Federico Leighton, Brian Poole, et al., "The Large-Scale Separation of Peroxisomes, Mitochondria, and Lysosomes from the Livers of Rats Injected with Triton WR-1339", 1968 (Box 60)
- Reprint, Michael J. Warburton and Brian Poole, "Effect of Medium Composition on Protein Degradation and DNA Synthesis in Rat Embryo Fibroblasts", 1977 (Box 60)
- Reprint, Brian Poole and Maurice Wibo, "Protein Degradation in Cultured Cells", 1973 (Box 60)
- Reprint, J. W. Coffey and Christian de Duve, "Digestive Activity of Lysosomes. I. The Digestion of Proteins by Extracts of Rat Liver Lysosomes", 1968 (Box 60)
- Reprint, William A. Dunn, Jon H. LaBadie and Nathan N. Aronson, Jr., "Inhibition of 125I-Asialofetuin Catabolism by Leupeptin in the Perfused Rat Liver and In Vivo", 1979 (Box 60)
- Reprint, Brian Poole, "Diffusion Effects in the Metabolism of Hydrogen Peroxide by Rat Liver Peroxisomes", 1975 (Box 60)
- Reprint, G.L. Gaunt and Christian de Duve, "Subcellular Distribution of D-Amino Acid Oxidase and Catalase in Rat Brain", 1976 (Box 60)
- Reprint, Stanley Fowler, Helen Shio, and Harvey Wolinsky, "Subcellular Fractionation and Morphology of Calf Aortic Smooth Muscle Cells", 1977 (Box 60)
- Reprint, Brian Poole, "Biogenesis and Turnover of Rat Liver Peroxisomes", 1969 (Box 60)
- Reprint, Christian de Duve, Thierry de Barsy, et al., "Commentary-Lysosomotropic Agents", 1974 (Box 60)
- Reprint, T.J. Peters, M. Müller and Christian de Duve, "Lysosomes of the Arterial Wall. I. Isolation and Subcellular Fractionation of Cells from Normal Rabbit Aorta", 1972 (Box 60)
- Abstract, Michael J. Warburton and Brian Poole, "Control of Growth and Protein Degradation in Rat Embryo Fibroblasts", 1977 (Box 60)
- Reprint, Shoji Ohkuma and Brian Poole, "Fluorescence Probe Measurement of the Intralysosomal pH in Living Cells and the Perturbation of pH by Various Agents", 1978 (Box 60)
- Reprint, Elizabeth Davidson and Brian Poole, "Fractionation of the Rat Liver Enzymes that Hydrolyze Benzoyl-Arginine-2-Naphthylamide", 1975 (Box 60)
- Reprint, Elizabeth Davidson, Stanley Fowler, and Brian Poole, "An Automated Method for Fluorescamine Reaction Using a Peristaltic Pump", 1975 (Box 60)
- Reprint, Pierre Baudhuin, Miklós Müller, Brian Poole, and Christian de Duve, "Non-Mitochondrial Oxidizing Particles (Microbodies) in Rat Liver and Kidney and in Tetrahymena Pyriformis", 1965 (Box 60)
- Reprint, Christian de Duve, "Is There a Glycolytic Particle?", 1972 (Box 60)
- Reprint, Christian de Duve and Pierre Baudhuin, "Peroxisomes (Microbodies and Related Particles)", 1966 (Box 60)
- Reprint, Christian de Duve and Robert Wattiaux, "The Function of Lysosomes", 1966 (Box 60)
- Reprint, Brian Poole, "The Stimulus to Hypertophic Growth", 1966 (Box 60)
- Reprint, B. Poole, S. Ohkuma and M.J. Warburton, "The Accumulation of Weakly Basic Substances in Lysosomes and the Inhibition of Intracellular Protein Degradation", 1977 (Box 60)
- Reprint, B. Poole, "Sythesis and Degradation of Proteins in Relation to Cellular Structure", 1971 (Box 60)
- Reprint, Christian de Duve, "Tissue Fractionation-Past and Present", 1971 (Box 60)
- Reprint, Brian Poole, Federico Leighton and Christian de Duve, "The Synthesis and Turnover of Rat Liver Peroxisomes. II. Turnover of Peroxisome Proteins", 1969 (Box 60)
- Reprint, Marco Baggiolini, James G. Hirsch, and Christian de Duve, "Resolution of Granules from Rabbit Heterophil Leukocytes into Distinct Populations by Zonal Sedimentation", 1969 (Box 60)
- Reprint, Brian Poole, "The Kinetics of Disappearance of Labeled Leucine from the Free Leucine Pool of Rat Liver and Its Effect on the Apparent Turnover of Catalase and Other Hepatic Proteins", 1971 (Box 60)
- Notes on Bioenergetics (Box 60)
- Partial Manuscript, Untitled (Box 60)
- Miscellaneous Rockefeller University (RU) Publications, 1976-1988 (Box 60)
- Matlin, Karl, Bioenergetics, 1974 (Box 60)
- Bioenergetics, Course Notes (Box 60)
- Notes, Bioenergetics (Box 60)
- Bioenergetics (Box 60)
- Bioenergetics Notes (Box 60)
- Notes on Bioenergetics (Box 60)
- Lab Notebook, Structure of Mitochondria (Box 61)
- D-Amino Acid Oxidase, Sellinger, Book 2, Rat Epididymis (Box 61)
- Lectures, Laboratory Problems (Box 61)
- Théorie de la centrifugation, 1957 (Box 61)
- Oxidative Phosphorylation Mitochondrial Swelling, 1959 (Box 61)
- Bibliography (Box 61)
- Untitled Laboratory Notebook, 1971 (Box 61)
- Aidolase, 1969 (Box 61)
- Manuscript Notes and Corrections (Box 61)
- Notes and Index Cards, 1977 (Box 61)
- Photographs, Leucine-Peroxisome, 1969 (Box 61)
- Peroxydation, 1967 (Box 61)
- Trouet/Assay (Box 61)
- Nick- 5(1) Nucleotidase Summary (Box 61)
- Lysosome F (Box 61)
- Lysosomal epase (Box 61)
- Untitled Notes, 1971 (Box 61)
- New York (Box 61)
- Information, 1969 (Box 61)
- Miscellaneous Experimental Results (Box 61)
- Notes, Cholesteryl Ester Hydrolase Assay, 1972 (Box 61)
- Adenylate Kinase (Box 61)
- "Neutral Protease", Bowers Article for Dingle and Fell (Box 61)
- Turnover Catalase, 1968 (Box 61)
- Catalase Activation Theory (Box 61)
- Peroxisomes, Notes and Documentation (Box 61)
- Documentation, 1972 (Box 61)
- Pinocytosis Notes, 1978 (Box 61)
- Theory of Turnover (Box 61)
- Theorie Mitochondries (Box 61)
- Wallach Model (Box 61)
- Allotheory, 1965 (Box 61)
- Cellular Pathology, 1969 (Box 61)
- Bowers, 1968 (Box 61)
- Historical Documents, 1967 (Box 61)
- Les Lipides (Box 61)
- Acides Nucleiques (Box 61)
- Acides Nucleiques (Box 61)
- Bioenergetique (Box 61)
- Les Grandes Voies Cataboliques (Box 61)
- Structure des Proteines (Box 61)
- JBBC Paper, "Tissue Fractionation Past and Present", Photographs (Box 61)
- Reprint, Nobukazu Araki and Kazuo Ogawa: "In Situ and In Vitro Morphological Evidence for the Interaction of Actin Filaments with Lysosomes in Rat Alveolar Macrophanges", 1987 (Box 61)
- Negative, Evolutionary History of C. pasteurianum Ferredoxin, 1966 (Box 61)
- Rockefeller University (RU) Publications, 1977-1978, 1987 (Box 61)
- Manuscript, "Blueprint for a Cell", Chapter 1, 1989 (Box 61)
- Manuscript, "Blueprint for a Cell", Chapter 2, 1989 (Box 61)
- Manuscript, "Blueprint for a Cell", Chapter 3, 1989 (Box 61)
- Manuscript, "Blueprint for a Cell", Chapter 4, 1989 (Box 61)
- Manuscript, "Blueprint for a Cell", Chapter 7, 1989 (Box 61)
- Reprints and Articles by André Trouet, 1979-1980 (Box 62)
- Chimiolysoso, 1980 (Box 62)
- Miscellaneous Sketches and Graphs (Box 62)
- Manuscript, "Blueprint for a Cell", Chapter 1, 1989 (Box 62)
- Reprint, "Alex Novikoff-Reminiscences"The Journal of Histochemistry and Cytochemistry, 1987 (Box 62)
- New York, Pending, 1982-1983 (Box 62)
- Manuscript, "Blueprint for a Cell", Chapter 1, 1989 (Box 62)
- Manuscript, "Blueprint for a Cell", Chapter 2, 1989 (Box 62)
- Manuscript, "Blueprint for a Cell", Chapter 3, 1989 (Box 62)
- Manuscript, "Blueprint for a Cell", Chapter 4, 1989 (Box 62)
- Manuscript, "Blueprint for a Cell", Chapter 5, 1989 (Box 62)
- Manuscript, "Blueprint for a Cell", Chapter 5, 1989 (Box 62)
- Manuscript, "Blueprint for a Cell", Chapter 5, 1989 (Box 62)
- Correspondence, Andre T. Jagendorf to E.C. Albritton, 1966 (Box 62)
- Ernster, Festschrift, 1980 (Box 62)
- Manuscript, Maurice Wibo, Denise Thines-Sempoux, et al., "Analytical Study of Microsomes and Isolated Subcellular Membranes from Rat Liver. VIII. Subfractionation of Preparations Enriched with Plasma Membranes, Outer Mitochondrial Membranes, and Golgi Membranes" (Box 62)
- Manuscript, Alain Amar-Costesec and Henri Beaufey, "A Structural Basis of Enzymic Heterogeneity within Liver Endoplasmic Reticulum" (Box 62)
- Correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 62)
- International Life Sciences Institute (ILSI) (Box 62)
- International Life Sciences Institute (ILSI) (Box 62)
- United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization (UNESCO) (Box 62)
- International Life Sciences Institute (ILSI) (Box 62)
- Medawar (Box 62)
- Princesse Liliane (Box 62)
- Princesse Liliane (Box 62)
- Manuscript, "Le Lysosome", Archives de Biologie, 1980 (Box 62)
- Manuscript, Schneider, et al., 1980 (Box 62)
- Manuscript, "A Short History of Tissue Fractionation" (Box 62)
- Manuscript, "Entretien Avec le Professeur de Duve (Box 62)
- International Life Sciences Institute (ILSI), 1963-1965 (Box 62)
- Manuscript, "Blueprint for a Cell", Chapter 5 (Box 63)
- Manuscript, "Blueprint for a Cell", Chapter 5 (Box 63)
- Manuscript, "Blueprint for a Cell", Chapter 1 (Box 63)
- Manuscript, "Blueprint for a Cell", 1987 (Box 63)
- Subject File, Lysosomotropic Chemotherapy, Experimental Work, 1972-1980 (Box 63)
- Reprint, Christian de Duve, "Constraints on the Origin and Evolution of Life", 1998 (Box 63)
- UPAC-IUB (International Union of Pure and Applied Chemistry-International Union of Biochemistry) Commission on Biochemical Nomenclature, 1975-1978 (Box 63)
- Reprint, P. C. Williams, "Suggestions for Speakers and Standards for Slides", 1965 (Box 63)
- World Health Organization (WHO) Reports, 1977 March 7-9 (Box 63)
- Dahlem Workshop on Transport of Macromolecules in Cellular Systems, Background Papers, 1978 April 24-28 (Box 63)
- Pasteels, J.J., "Pinocytose et athrocytose…" (Index Cards), 1968 (Box 63)
- Correspondence, Cancer Institute and Publications, 1975-1980 (Box 63)
- Reprint, Christian de Duve, "Exploring Cells with a Centrifuge", 1975 (Box 63)
- Extra Material, Of Historical Interest, 1935-1982 (Box 63)
- Thesis, J. D. Castle, "Studies on the Secretory Process of the Rabbit Parotid", 1973 (Box 63)
- Glass Slides (Box 64)
- Glass Slides (Box 64)
- Glass Slides (Box 64)
- Glass Slides (Box 64)
- Glass Slides (Box 64)
- Glass Slides (Box 64)
- Glass Slides (Box 64)
- Projector Slides (Box 64)
- Slide Binder, Pathology, Aging Storage Atherosc. (Box 64)
- Slide Binder, Centrif. Fraction Early Results Misc. Part., Protozoa (Box 64)
- Slide Binder, Lysosomes (Box 64)
- Slide Binder, Pharmacology Therapy-pH-Prot. T4 (Box 65)
- Slide Binder, Peroxisomes (Box 65)
- Slide Binder, Historical (Box 65)
- Slide Binder, Rolodex (Box 65)
- Slide Binder, Projector Slides (Box 65)
- Slide Binder, Projector Slides (Box 65)
- Slide Binder, Projector Slides (Box 65)
- Slide Binder, Projector Slides (Box 65)
- Slide Binder, Projector Slides (Box 65)
- Slide Binder, Projector Slides (Box 65)
- Scully Rencontre Kissinger Version Anglaise (VHS Tape), 1994 September 13 (Box 65)
- Poole, Brian, Tape 1 (Audio Cassette) (Box 65)
- Poole, Brian, Tape 2 (Audio Cassette) (Box 65)
- Poole, Brian, Tape 3 (Audio Cassette) (Box 65)
- Poole, Brian, Tape 4 (Audio Cassette) (Box 65)
- Poole, Brian, Tape 5 (Audio Cassette) (Box 65)
- Magnabelts (Box 65)
- Magnabelts (Box 65)
- Magnabelts (Box 65)
- Index Cards, A-G (Box 66)
- Rolodex (Box 66)
- Index Cards (Box 66)
- Index Cards (Box 66)
- Index Cards (Box 66)
- Index Cards (Box 66)
- Index Cards (Box 66)
- Index Cards (Box 66)
- Index Cards (Box 66)
- Index Cards (Box 66)
- Index Cards (Box 66)
- Index Cards, R-G (Box 67)
- Rolodex (Box 67)
- Index Cards (Box 67)
- Index Cards (Box 67)
- Publication, Pontifical Academy of Sciences, 1985-1986 (Box 68)
- Publication, Pierre Baudhuin, "L'Analyse Morphologique Quantitative De Fractions Subecellualar", 1968 (Box 68)
- Publication, André Truouet: "La Chimothérapie Lysosomotrope des Leucémies" (Box 68)
- Index Cards (Box 68)
- Unlabeled Transparancies (Box 68)
- Oaxaca Transparencies (Box 68)
- Unlabeled Transparencies (Box 68)
- Unlabeled Transparencies (Box 68)
- Glass Slide (Box 68)
- Correspondence, The Clinical Research Institute of Montreal (Box 68)
- Galley Proofs, T.J. Peters' Book on Subcellular Pathology of Systemic Disease (Box 68)
- Reprint, Christian de Duve, "Alex Novicoff-Reminiscences", 1987 (Box 68)
- Publication, The Harvey Society Lectures, 1969-1970 (Box 68)
- Publication, Helene J. Waddell, Manuscript, "Blueprint for a Cell", 1988 (Box 68)
- Publication, Christian de Duve, "The Future of Experimental Biology in Medical Research", 1986 (Box 68)
- Rockefeller University (RU) Publications, 1969-1977 (Box 68)
- Publication, Scientific American, Christian de Duve, "Microbodies in the Living Cell" (Box 68)
- Publication, Singularities (Box 69)
- Publication, ICP Scientific Reports, 1974-1997 (Box 69)
- Publication, International Institute of Cellular and Molecular Pathology, Report (Box 69)
- Publications des Chercheurs du Laboratoire de Chimie Physiologique, Volumes I-V, 1948-1966 (Box 70)
- Publication, "Les Inhibiteurs de L'Aromatisation des Androgenes Implications Physiologiques et Therapeautiques", 1982 (Box 70)
- Publication, "Mise au Point de Derives Lysosomotropes de la Primaquine par Association a des Liposomes et par Couplage et l'Asialofetuine", 1982 (Box 70)
- Pubication, "Etude du Sort de la Membrane Plasmique au Cours de l'Endocytose", 1976 (Box 70)
- Publication, Harvey Lectures: Series 71-73, 1975-1978 (Box 70)
- Publication, An Era in New York Biochemistry (Box 70)
- Publication, Publications des Chercheurs du Laboratoire de Chimie Physiologique, Volumes VI-VII, 1966-1970 (Box 71)
- Publication, Publications des Chercheurs du Laboratoire de Chimie Physiologique et du Laboratory of Biochemical Cytology, Volumes VIII-XIII, 1971-1978 (Box 71)
- Publication, Publications des Chercheurs du Laboratoire de Chimie Physiologique, Volumes XIV-XVI, 1979-1981 (Box 72)
- Publication, Publications of the Laboratory of Biochemical Cytology (Rockefeller University (RU)), 1969-1988 (Box 72)
- Publication, ICP Informational Booklet (Box 73)
- Publication, ICP Publications, 1982 (Box 73)
- Publication, Cellular Injury, CIBA Foundation Symposium, 1963 (Box 73)
- Publication, "Nongonococcal Urethritis and Other Selected Sexually Transmitted Diseases of Public Health Importance", Contributor, Miklos Müller, WHO Technical Report Series 660, 1981 (Box 73)
- Dissertation, "Localisation Intracellulaire et Biosynthese du Cytochrome C de Foie de Rat", Mariette Robbi, 1975 (Box 73)
- Dissertation, "Renouvellement dese Proteines des Lysosomes et des Autres Organites Intracellulaires du Foie de Rat": Renée Cassir, 1962 (Box 73)
- Dissertation, "Characterization of Rat Liver Proteases", Elizabeth Davidson (Box 73)
- Dissertation, Thesis, "Hydrogenosomes and Carbohydrate Metabolism in Tritrchmonas Foetus", Elizabeth Davidson (Box 73)
- Dissertation, "Les Lipides des Lysosomes et D'Autres Constituants Subcellulaires", Denyse Thinès-Sempoux, 1968 (Box 73)
- Dissertation, "Propriétés pharmacodynamiques cellulaires de la daunorubicine et de l'adriamycine, libres et complexées à l'ADN", Guy Noël, 1974 (Box 73)
- Dissertation, "A Biochemical Characterization of Rat Spleen Lysosomes and Lysosomes from Other Lymphoid Tissues", William E. Bowers, 1966 (Box 73)
- Dissertation, "Studies on Rat Liver Peroxisomes", Brian Poole, 1968 (Box 73)
- Dissertation, "Lipolytic Activities of Rat Liver Lysosomes", Stanley Dee Fowler, 1969 (Box 73)
- Dissertation, "Subcellular Localization of D-Amino Acid Oxidase in Rat Brain", George Loren Gaunt, 1973 (Box 73)
- Dissertation, "Influences Hormonales sur le Metabolisme des Phospholipides dans des Tissus Isoles", Gertrudis de Torrontegui, 1963 (Box 73)
- Dissertation, "La Chimiothérapie Lysosomotrope des Leucémies", André Trouet (Box 73)